Inventory of the Jo Ann Davis Papers 2001-2007
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Jo Ann Davis Papers 2001-2007 2001-2006
Special Collections Research Center
01/Mss. Acc. 2007.111
29.00
Davis, Jo Ann, 1950-2007 arrangement
Administrative Information
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open to all researchers.
Acquisition Information
The materials were acquired by Special Collections Research Center on 00/00/2007.
Biographical Note
Jo Ann Davis was born in 1950 near Salisbury, North Carolina and moved to Hampton, Virginia when she was 9 years old. She was living in Gloucester, Virginia at the time of her death.Jo Ann Davis was Virginia's first female Republican in Congress, elected in 2000 as the Representative from Virginia's First District. She was a strong leader in national security issues, shipbuilding, veterans and the Chesapeake Bay. She was in her fourth term when she died of breast cancer in 2007. She was on the Foreign Affairs and Armed Services Committees. Before she became a Congresswoman, she owned real estate businesses and represented York County in the Virginia House of Delegates in 1997. She was known for her humble roots, Christian beliefs and love of the outdoors. Further information about this individual or organization may be available in the Special Collections Research Center Wiki: http://scrc.swem.wm.edu/wiki/index.php/Jo Ann Davis.
Scope and Contents
Papers of United States Representative Jo Ann Davis, Congresswoman from Virginia's First District from 2000 to 2007. The Papers are mostly legislative material where she was involved either as an originator of or co-signer to Dear Colleague letters or as a sponsor or co-sponsor to legislation, but also includes speeches, press releases and office files.The first folder is the first box contains news clippings, biographical information, list of staff members and definitions of Co-Sign, Sign-On and Dear Colleague Letters.
Arrangement of Materials
The files are divided into Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters and Co-sponsored Legislation, Congressional Sessions, Legislative Matters, Publicity, Constituents and Office Files. Most files are in chronological order, though there are exceptions.
Additional Information
Index Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
United States Congress
Genre/Form of Material:
Correspondence; Press releases; Reports; Speeches
Topical Term:
Memorandums; Military Affairs - United States; Virginia--Politics and Government.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Legislative Material, 2000-2007; id54896
  - id49996 (Box 1)
    - Co-Sign and Dear Colleague Letters and Co-Sponsored Legislation, 2000-2007; id23051 (Box 1, Sub-series 1)
      - Co-sponsored Legislation and Co-sign Letters – Vaughn Murphy, 2001-2003; id23052 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 1)
      - Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters, 2002; id23053 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 2)
      - Co-sponsored Legislation, 2002; id23119 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 3)
      - Co-sponsored Legislation and Co-sign Letters – Tim, 2002; id23120 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 4)
      - Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters, 2003; id23121 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 5)
      - Co-Sponsored Legislation, 2003; id23122 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 6)
      - Co-sponsored Legislation and Sign-On Letters – Tim Baroody, 2003; id23123 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 7)
      - Co-Sponsored Legislation and Co-sign Letters – Jonathan Kidwell, 2003; id23124 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 8)
      - Co-sponsored Legislation and Sign-On Letters – Melissa Smith, January - April 2003; id23125 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 9)
      - Co-sponsored Legislation and Sign-On Letters – Melissa Smith, May - July 2003; id23126 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 10)
      - Co-sponsored Legislation and Sign-On Letters – Melissa Smith, August - December 2003; id23127 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 11)
      - Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters – Melissa Smith, 2004; id23129 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 12)
      - Co-Sponsored Legislation – Melissa Smith, 2004; id23137 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 13)
      - Co-Sponsored Legislation and Co-sign Letters, 2004; id23138 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 14)
      - Co-Sponsored Legislation and Co-sign Letters – John Fleet, 2004; id23139 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 15)
      - Co-Sponsored Legislation – Brent Robinson File, 2004; id23140 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 16)
      - Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters, January – April 2005; id23141 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 17)
      - Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters, May - December 2005; id23142 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 18)
      - Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters – Melissa Smith Clements, 2005; id23143 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 19)
      - Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters – Brent Robinson, 2005; id23144 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 20)
      - Co-Sponsored Legislation, 2005; id23145 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 21)
      - Co-Sponsored Legislation – Jonathan Kidwell, 2005; id23146 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 22)
      - Co-Sponsored Legislation – Brent Robinson, 2005; id23147 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 23)
      - Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters, 2006; id23148 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 24)
      - Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters and Cosponsored Legislation – By subject – A – H, 2006; id23149 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 25)
      - Co-sign and Dear Colleague Letters and Cosponsored Legislation – By subject – I - Z, 2006; id23150 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 26)
      - Co-sponsored Legislation, 2007; id23151 (Box 1, Sub-series 1, Folder 27)
  - id49997 (Box 2)
    - Congressional Sessions, 2001-2007; id23152 (Box 2, Sub-series 2)
      - 107th Congress – 1st Session- Co-Sponsorships, January - March 2001; id23170 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 1)
      - 107th Congress – 1st Session- Co-Sponsorships, April - May 2001; id23171 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 2)
      - 107th Congress – 1st Session- Co-Sponsorships, June - December 2001; id23172 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 3)
      - 107th Congress – 1st Session - Legislative Activity Guide of Honorable Jo Ann Davis, January – June 2001; id23173 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 4)
      - 107th Congress – 2nd Session - Co-Sponsorships, January – May 2002; id23174 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 5)
      - 107th Congress – 2nd Session - Co-Sponsorships, June 2002; id23175 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 6)
      - 107th Congress – 2nd Session - Co-Sponsorships, July - December 2002; id23176 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 7)
      - 107th Congress - Co-Sponsorships - JAD Co-sponsorships of Federal Employee Related Legislation in the 107th Congress, 2001; id23177 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 8)
      - 107th Congress – Legislation – Legislative Profile, January 3, 2001 – August 6, 2001; id23178 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 9)
      - 107th Congress – Legislation – Legislative Profile, January 3, 2001 – December 31, 2001; id23179 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 10)
      - 107th Congress – Legislation – Legislative Profile, January 3, 2001 – December 31, 2002; id23180 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 11)
      - 107th Congress – Voting Record (Legislative Activity Guide) for January – December 2001, February 1, 2002; id23181 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 12)
      - 108th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2003; id23182 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 13)
      - 108th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2003; id23183 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 14)
      - 108th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2003; id23184 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 15)
      - 108th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2003; id23185 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 16)
      - 108th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2003; id23186 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 17)
      - 108th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2003; id23187 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 18)
      - 108th Congress – 2nd Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2004; id23188 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 19)
      - 108th Congress – 2nd Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2004; id23189 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 20)
      - 108th Congress – 2nd Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2004; id23190 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 21)
      - 108th Congress – Legislation - Co-sponsored and Sponsored Legislation by Congresswoman Jo Ann Davis – Sorted by Bill Name and Number, 2004; id23191 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 22)
      - 109th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2005; id23192 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 23)
      - 109th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, January - June 2005; id23193 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 24)
      - 109th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, July - December 2005; id23194 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 25)
      - 109th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, January - May 2005; id23195 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 26)
      - 109th Congress – 1st Session - Co-Sponsorships, June - December 2005; id23196 (Box 2, Sub-series 2, Folder 27)
  - id49998 (Box 3)
    - Congressional Sessions 2001-2007, id50135 (Box 3, Sub-series 2)
      - 109th Congress – 2nd Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2006; id23197 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 1)
      - 109th Congress – 2nd Session - Co-Sponsorships, 2006; id23198 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 2)
      - 109th Congress – Reports – Legislation by Congresswoman Jo Ann Davis, 2005; id23199 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 3)
      - 109th Congress – Reports – Legislation by Congresswoman Jo Ann Davis, 2005; id23200 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 4)
      - 109th Congress – Reports – Legislation by Congresswoman Jo Ann Davis, May 2005; id23201 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 5)
      - 109th Congress – Reports – Legislation by Congresswoman Jo Ann, May 2005; id23202 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 6)
      - 109th Congress – Reports – Legislation by Congresswoman Jo Ann Davis, May 2005; id23203 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 7)
      - 109th Congress - Rules of the House of Representatives by Jeff Trandahl, Clerk of the House of Representatives, 2005; id23289 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 8)
      - 109th Congress – 2nd Session to 110th Congress – 1st Session - Legislation, 2006-2007; id23290 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 9)
      - 109th Congress – 2nd Session to 110th Congress – 1st Session - Legislation, 2006-2007; id23291 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 10)
      - 109th Congress – 2nd Session to 110th Congress – 1st Session - Legislation, 2006-2007; id23292 (Box 3, Sub-series 2, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Matters, 2002-2007; id23293 (Box 3, Sub-series 3)
      - John Ashcroft vs American Civil Liberties Union, et al, 12/10/2003; id23295 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 11)
      - Boy Scouts - Jamboree Amicus Brief, 2005; id23296 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 12)
      - Boy Scouts – Winkler v. Rumsfeld, November 2005; id23297 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 13)
      - BRAC Task Force – First District of Virginia, 2002; id23298 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 14)
      - Committees – Armed Services Committee Hearings, 2005-2006; id23299 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 15)
      - Committees – Armed Services Committee Hearings, 2006; id23300 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 16)
      - Committees – Civil Service and Agency Organization Subcommittee, 2003; id23301 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 17)
      - Committees – Assignments, 2007; id23302 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence - Legislative Matters, 2001-2003; id23303 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence - Legislative Matters, 2004-2007; id23304 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 20)
      - Jamestown Coin, H.R. 1914, 2003; id23305 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 21)
      - Homeland Security (Byrne) Government Reform Testimony, 2003; id23306 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 22)
      - Legislation – Introduced by Jo Ann Davis: FEMA (Federal Emergency Management Agency) and NFIP (National Flood Insurance Program), 2004-2006; id23307 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 23)
      - Legislation - Introduced by Jo Ann Davis - Northern Neck National Heritage Area, id23308 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 24)
      - Legislation - Introduced by Jo Ann Davis - Captain John Smith Chesapeake National Historic Water Trail, 2004-2006; id23309 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 25)
      - Legislation - Introduced by Jo Ann Davis - Captain John Smith Chesapeake National Historical Trail – Letters of Support and Thanks, 2006; id23310 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 26)
      - Legislative Highlights and Votes of Jo Ann Davis, 2002-2005; id23311 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 27)
      - Legislative Concerns - News Clippings, 2003 and 2005; id23312 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 28)
      - Memberships, 2001 and undated; id23313 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 29)
      - Petroleum Usage, Executive Order 13149, 2002; id23314 (Box 3, Sub-series 3, Folder 30)
  - id54897 (Box 4)
    - Legislative Matters, 2002-2007, id50136 (Box 4, Sub-series 3)
      - Redundancy Bill, 2004; id23316 (Box 4, Sub-series 3, Folder 1)
      - Republican Freshman Class Orientation, November 2000; id23317 (Box 4, Sub-series 3, Folder 2)
      - “Salute to the Military Pass in Review, “Yorktown, Virginia - Invitation to President George W. Bush, 2006; id23318 (Box 4, Sub-series 3, Folder 3)
      - Statements – Floor, Committee and Hearing Statements, 2001-2006; id23319 (Box 4, Sub-series 3, Folder 4)
      - Task Force – Brent Robinson, 2004-2005; id23320 (Box 4, Sub-series 3, Folder 5)
      - Transatlantic Legislators’ Dialogue, 1-16 - Held in Williamsburg, VA, November 2003; id23321 (Box 4, Sub-series 3, Folder 6)
      - NRCC Issues Book 2006, id23322 (Box 4, Sub-series 3, Folder 7)
      - Voting Record of Jo Ann Davis During Illness, 2007; id23323 (Box 4, Sub-series 3, Folder 8)
- Publicity Files, 2001-2007; id54898
  - id54899 (Box 4)
    - Holiday Greeting/Thank You Advertisements, Undated; id54909 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Interview Questions and Answers, 2003 and undated.; id54910 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Letters to the Editor, 2001-2006; id54911 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases, 2001-2002; id54912 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases, 2003-2007; id54913 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Grants – Press Releases, 2002-June 2003; id54914 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Grants – Press Releases, September 2003 – January 2004; id54916 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Press Releases – by Subject, 2001-2007; id54917 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Speeches and Remarks to Groups, 2001-2004 and undated; id54918 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Speeches and Remarks to Groups, 2005-2006; id54919 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Statements by Jo Ann Davis, 2001-2005; id54920 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Talking Point and Briefings to Jo Ann Davis from Staff Members, id54921 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Constituents, 2003-2007 and undated.; id54902
  - id54907 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence with or concerning Constituents, 2001-2007 and undated; id23340 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - District Meetings, 2005; id23341 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Flyers, Pamphlets and Mailings, undated; id23342 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Newsletters and E-Newsletters, 2006; id23343 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Tele-Town Hall, 2007; id23344 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Town Hall Meetings, 2003-04, undated; id23345 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Office Files, 2001-2007 and undated.; id54904
  - id54908 (Box 4)
    - Financial Donations - Tom DeLay, undated; id23347 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Guest Book, Begins January 3, 2001; id23348 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Guest Book, 2002-October 2007; id23349 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - National Prayer Breakfast, 2005; id23350 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - National Prayer Breakfast – Chair’s Notebook, 2007; id23351 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Office Matters, 2002-2006; id23352 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Carl E. Waltz Photograph, Autographed, undated; id23353 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - White House Visit, 2004; id23354 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Legislative Concerns, Local Issues, 2001 and undated; id54923
  - id54924 (Box 5)
    - Support for Shays-Meehan/McCain-Feingold, id54925 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Pro-Life General, id54926 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Customs Border Security Act-Con, id54927 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Family Planning-Pro, id54928 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Truth in Employment Act-Pro, id54929 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Truth in Employment Act-Pro, id54930 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Ten Commandments Protection Act, id54931 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 9/11 Immigration, id54932 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Glacier Bay, id54934 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Army Pilots-Pro, id54935 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Anti-Cloning, id54936 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Boehlert-Kind Amendment, id54937 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Airline Carriers-Poultry Letters, id54939 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 534, Project Exile, id54940 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Second Amendment Rights-Pro, id54941 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Bush Energy Plan-Con Part I, id54942 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Bush Energy Plan-Con Part II, id54943 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Bush Energy Plan-Con Part III, id54944 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Born Alive Infant Protection-Pro, id54945 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - H.R. 503 Unborn Victims of Violence Act-Pro, id54946 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Interstate Waste- Part I, id54947 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Interstate Waster- Part II, id54948 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Shays-Meehan/McCain-Feingold- Con Part I, id54949 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Shays-Meehan/McCain-Feingold- Con Part II, id54950 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Working Lands Stewardship Act, id54951 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - H.R. 1455-Pro (Goode’s Gun Bill), id54952 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - H.R. 7-Con (Faith-Based), id54954 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - King William Reservoir- Con, id54955 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Hate Crimes in H.R. 1- Con, id54956 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Boy Scouts- Pro, id54957 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Kyoto Protocol- Pro, id54958 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Kyoto Protocol- Con, id54959 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Death Penalty Moratorium- 3/1/01, id54960 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Hostettler’s Pro-Gun Letter 3/16/01, id54961 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Pro-Gun 3/23/01, id54962 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Pro-Environment Faxes and Letters 1/30/01, id54963 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Endocrine Screening Research, id54964 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - NIH-Animal Testing- Con, id54965 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Right-to-Work, id54967 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Anti-Illegal Immigration, id54968 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Pro-Civil-Rights Re Terrorism, id54969 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Flag Burning Amendment- Con, id54970 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Flag Burning Amendment- Pro, id54971 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Campaign Finance Reform- Con, id54972 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Campaign Finance Reform- Pro, id54973 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - id54974 (Box 6)
    - Federal Employee Contraceptives- Pro, id54976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Employment Non-Discrimination Act 8/2/01, id54977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Embryonic Stem Cell Research- Pro, id54978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Inexpensive Book Distribution Program- Pro 6/4/01, id54980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Pro School Choice in H.R. 1 6/11/01, id54981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 1- Con, id54982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Farm Bill Meeting Invitation 4/4 and 4/11, id54983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 950- Pro (Hostettler’s Gun Bill), id54984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Executive Order 13166- Con, id54985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Motor Voter- Con (Support H.R. 189), id54986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Interstate Waste (Part III), id54987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - King William Reservoir- Pro, id54988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Campaign Finance Reform- Con (Entered in CapCorr) I, id54989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Campaign Finance Reform- Con (Entered in CapCorr) II, id54990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Equal Protection of Voting Rights Act, id54991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - “Go Girls” Act, id54992 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Oyster Reef Funding, id54993 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 331- Pro (Remove Davis-Bacon Requirement from Public School Construction), id54994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Real Estate – Financial Services Rule March 1, 2001, id54996 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Real Estate – Financial Services, id54997 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Constituents Correspondence, 2001; id55002
  - A-B, id55015 (Box 7)
  - B-C, id55016 (Box 8)
  - C-D, id55017 (Box 9)
  - D-G, id55018 (Box 10)
  - G-H, id55019 (Box 11)
  - H-J, id55020 (Box 12)
  - J-L, id55021 (Box 13)
  - L-M, id55022 (Box 14)
  - M-P, id55023 (Box 15)
  - P-R, id55024 (Box 16)
  - R-S, id55025 (Box 17)
  - S-V, id55026 (Box 18)
  - V-Z, id55027 (Box 19)
- Constituents Correspondence, 2002; id55028
  - A-B, id55029 (Box 20)
  - B-C, id55030 (Box 21)
  - C-F, id55031 (Box 22)
  - F-H, id55032 (Box 23)
  - H-J, id55033 (Box 24)
  - K-L, id55034 (Box 25)
  - M, id55035 (Box 26)
  - M-R, id55036 (Box 27)
  - R-S, id55037 (Box 28)
  - S-Z, id55038 (Box 29)